A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.34 (A2008) FA493
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.34 (A2008)
1988-2005
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA493
36.68 Cubic Feet 28 standard record storage boxes, R3874-R3901
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (digital media) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Scope and Contents
Grant administration files and related material.
- AC.2008.001: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2003; AC.2008.001; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3874-R3877.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2008.001.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 99033 - PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT DEMONSTRATION, 1994-2002 (Box R3874)
    - RF 99033 - PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT DEMONSTRATION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-2002 (Box R3874)
    - EF 99033 #61 - FLINT (CITY OF) SCHOOL DISTRICT - BUILDING AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 1994-2002 (Box R3874)
    - RF 99033 #62 - FLINT (CITY OF) SCHOOL DISTRICT - EVALUATION OF DISTRICT'S SCHOOL REFORM EFFORTS, 1999-2003 (Box R3874)
    - RF 99036 #6 - CARTER CENTER - ETHIOPIA PUBLIC HEALTH TRAINING INITIATIVE, 1998-2002 (Box R3875)
    - RF 99037 #3 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - GLOBAL HEALTH EQUITY INITIATIVE'S CONCEPTUAL GROUPS ON ETHICS, MEASUREMENT AND GENDER, 1997-2004 (Box R3875)
    - RF 99037 #9 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - HEALTH EQUITY GAUGE, 2000-2003 (Box R3875)
    - RF 99039 #8 - CAMBODIA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - DISEASE SURVEILLANCE NETWORK, 1999-2003 (Box R3875)
    - RF 99039 #9 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - KNOWLEDGE MANAGEMENT OF PUBLIC HEALTH IN SOUTHEAST ASIA, 2000-2003 (Box R3875)
    - RF 99040 - ACTION RESEARCH TO IMPROVE REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH SERVICE DELIVERY, 1991-2003 (Box R3875)
    - RF 99040 #102 - UNIVERSITY OF OUAGADOUGOU (BURKINA FASO) - ABORTION AND UNWANTED PREGNANCY IN RURAL AREAS, 2000-2004 (Box R3875)
    - RF 99042 - UNDERSTANDING DIVERSITY IN MUSLIM SOCIETIES, 1993-2000 (Box R3876)
    - RF 99042 - UNDERSTANDING DIVERSITY IN MUSLIM SOCIETIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2000 (Box R3876)
    - RF 99042 #78 - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION FOR THE STUDY OF PERSIAN-SPEAKING SOCIETIES - JOINT PLANNING COMMITTEE FOR IRAN, INDIA AND CENTRAL ASIA, 1998-2002 (Box R3876)
    - RF 99042 #81 - AL-URDUN AL-JADID RESEARCH CENTER (JORDAN) - SOCIAL HISTORY OF JORDAN, 1995-2002 (Box R3877)
    - RF 99042 #81 - AL-URDUN AL-JADID RESEARCH CENTER (JORDAN) - SOCIAL HISTORY OF JORDAN - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1995-2002 (Box R3877)
    - RF 99042 #85 - ROYAL INSTITUTE FOR INTER-FAITH STUDIES - CONFERENCE ON ISLAM AND SCIENCE, 2000-2003 (Box R3877)
    - RF 99044 #627 - HOWARD UNIVERSITY - SEMINAR ON SLAVERY IN A COMPARATIVE CONTEXT, 2000-2003 (Box R3877)
    - RF 99044 #631 - FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF MINAS GERAIS (BRAZIL) - CONFERENCES, "MARGINS (MARGENS/MARGENES)", 2000-2003 (Box R3877)
    - RF 99044 #632 - UNIVERSITY OF OREGON - CONFERENCE IN CONNECTION WITH RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS IN HUMANITIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3877)
    - RF 99044 #75 - SOCIAL AND PUBLIC ART RESOURCE CENTER - GREAT WALL OF LOS ANGELES MURAL, 2002-2003 (Box R3877)
- AC.2008.010: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2004; AC.2008.010; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3878.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2008.010.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage boxes
    - RF 99046 - CULTURE AND COMMUNITY BUILDING, 1995-2000 (Box R3878)
    - RF 99046 #13 - RAND CORP. - "INTEGRATIVE ASSESSMENT OF THE ARTS" STUDY, 2000-2003 (Box R3878)
    - RF 99052 - MILLENNIUM HEALTH RESEARCH AWARDS, 1999 (Box R3878)
    - RF 99052 #11 - HEALTH SYSTEMS RESEARCH INSTITUTE (THAILAND) - HEALTH RESEARCH AWARD, 2000-2004 (Box R3878)
    - RF 99053 - GLOBAL DIALOGUES ON PLANT BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1999 (Box R3878)
    - RF 99053 #1 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - BIOTECHNOLOGY AND THE GLOBAL ECONOMY, 1999-2003 (Box R3878)
- AC.2008.038: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1988-2005; AC.2008.038; 15.72 Cubic Feet 12 standard record storage boxes, R3879-R3890.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2008.038.1; 15.72 Cubic Feet 12 record storage boxes
    - RF 92102 - VIDEOCASSETTE DISTRIBUTION AND EXHIBITION, 1988-1997 (Box R3879)
    - RF 92102 - VIDEOCASSETTE DISTRIBUTION AND EXHIBITION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-1997 (Box R3879)
    - RF 94040 - NATIONAL VIDEO RESOURCES, INC., 1992-1997 (Box R3880)
    - RF 99047 - UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON - HISPANIC LITERARY HERITAGE OF THE U.S., 1991-2005 (Box R3881, Box R3880)
    - RF 99047 - UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON - HISPANIC LITERARY HERITAGE OF THE U.S. - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2005 (Box R3881, Box R3880)
    - RF 99048 - U.S. - MEXICO FUND FOR CULTURE - INTERACTION BETWEEN MEXICAN AND AMERICAN ARTISTS AND SCHOLARS, 1990-2004 (Box R3882, Box R3883, R3884, R3885, Box R3886)
    - RF 99048 - - U.S. - MEXICO FUND FOR CULTURE - INTERACTION BETWEEN MEXICAN AND AMERICAN ARTISTS AND SCHOLARS - ABIMEX - Antigua Bibliografia Mexicana - Digital, 2008:038:001 (Item 2008:038:001)
      Separated Materials
      Special format items (digital media) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    - RF 99048 - U.S. - MEXICO FUND FOR CULTURE - INTERACTION BETWEEN MEXICAN AND AMERICAN ARTISTS AND SCHOLARS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-2004 (Box R3882, Box R3883, R3884, R3885, Box R3886)
    - RF 98036 - AFRICAN DOCTORAL INTERSHIPS, 1987-2004 (Box R3887)
    - RF 98036 - AFRICAN DOCTORAL INTERSHIPS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-2004 (Box R3888)
    - RF 98036 - AFRICAN DOCTORAL INTERSHIPS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-2004 (Box R3889)
    - RF 98036 - AFRICAN DOCTORAL INTERSHIPS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-2004 (Box R3890)
- AC.2008.046: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2005; AC.2008.046; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 standard record storage boxes, R3891-R3897
  - Fellowships (F), AC.2008.046.1; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - F 94122 - (INDONESIA) (F-AS) AMIRHUSIN, BAHAGIAWATI, 1994-2000 (Box R3891)
    - F 96006 - (KENYA) (F-AS) AYAGA, GEORGE ODWAR, 1996-2000 (Box R3891)
    - F 96025 - (INDONESIA) (F-AS) ABDULLAH, BUANG, 1996-2001 (Box R3891)
    - F 96091 - (PHILIPPINES) (F-AS) ANDAYA, VIRGILIO CEDRO, 1996-2003 (Box R3891)
    - F 96092 - (PHILIPPINES) (F-AS) BATO ANDAYA, CYNTHIA, 1996-2003 (Box R3891)
    - F 97057 - (PHILIPPINES) (F-AS) ALFONSO, ANTONIO ANDRES, 1997-2003 (Box R3891)
    - F 98012 - (UGANDA) (F-AS) ABERA, AGNES M., 1998-2004 (Box R3891)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted - Open in 2025
    - F 98053 - (UGANDA) (F-AS) BWAMIKI, DAVID PATRICK, 1998-2004 (Box R3891)
    - F 98107 - (UGANDA) (F-AS) AJONYE, MARGARET, 1998-2002 (Box R3891)
    - F 99026 - (INDIA) (F-AS) AGRAWAL, PAWAN KUMAR, 1999-2001 (Box R3891)
    - F 99079 - (IVORY COAST) (F-AS) ALUKO, GABRIEL KAYODE, 1999-2003 (Box R3891)
    - F 94093 - (KENYA) (F-AS) CHEGE, DANIEL NG'ANG'A, 1994-2000 (Box R3892)
    - F 96028 - (UGANDA) (F-AS) EDEMA, RICHARD, 1996-2002 (Box R3892)
    - F 96036 - (KENYA) (F-AS) CHEGE, AYUB GEORGE GETHEYO, 1996-2001 (Box R3892)
    - F 97054 - (UGANDA ) (F-AS) GAHAKWA, DAPHROSE, 1997-2005 (Box R3892)
      Restricted - Open in 2026
    - F 97062 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) CHIKWAMBA, RACHEL, 1997-2003 (Box R3892)
    - F 97086 - (CHINA) (F-AS) FU XIANGDONG, 1997-2001 (Box R3892)
    - F 98034 - (THAILAND) (F-AS) VARAPONG CHAMARERK, 1998-2003 (Box R3892)
    - F 98054 - (MALAWl) (F-AS) CHIRWA, PAXIE WANANGA, 1998-2003 (Box R3892)
    - F 99006 - (CHINA ) (F-AS) FU XIQIN, 1999-2005 (Box R3892)
    - F 99023 - (INDIA) (F-AS) DHINGRA, AMIT, 1999-2001 (Box R3892)
    - F 95020 - (KENYA) (F-AS) KARANJA, DANIEL DAVID, 1995-2003 (Box R3893)
    - F 96001 - (UGANDA) (F-AS) KALYEBARA, ROBERT M., 1996-2001 (Box R3893)
    - F 98002 - (INDIA) (F-AS) KUKREJA, KAMLESH, 1998-2000 (Box R3893)
    - F 98021 - (KENYA) (F-AS) GETHI, JAMES G., 1998-2003 (Box R3893)
    - F 98035 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) GWATA, EASTONCE TENDAYI, 1998-2005 (Box R3893)
    - F 98044 - (INDIA) (F-AS) KANNAN BAPU, J.R., 1998-2001 (Box R3893)
    - F 98045 - (INDIA ) (F-AS) JOHN JOEL, AMALRAJ, 1998-2000 (Box R3893)
    - F 98072 - (IVORY COAST) (F-AS) KOKORA, RACHELLE NICOLE NATALIE, 1998-2005 (Box R3893)
    - F 99062 - (INDIA) (F-AS) GANESH, SIRUTHAIYUR, K., 1999-2001 (Box R3893)
    - F 99080 - (AUSTRALIA) (F-AS) HOANG THI KIM OANH, 1999-2002 (Box R3893)
    - 2000 FS 315 - (INDIA) (FAS) MAHENDRU, ANJU, 2000-2001 (Box R3894)
    - F 95012 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) MHARAPARA, ISIAH M., 1995-2001 (Box R3894)
    - F 97038 - (CHINA) (F-AS) LI XINQI, 1994-2000 (Box R3894)
    - F 98004 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) NGUYEN THI LOC, 1998-2001 (Box R3894)
    - F 98018 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) LOAN, LE CAM, 1998-2003 (Box R3894)
    - F 98032 - (CHINA) (F-AS) LIN XINGHUA, 1998-2001 (Box R3894)
    - F 98036 - (KENYA) (F-AS) MBUGUA, DAVID MWAURA, 1998-2003 (Box R3894)
    - F 99005 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) MURATA, MONICA RUJEKO, 1999-2003 (Box R3894)
    - F 99031 - (INDIA) (F-AS) MADHURI, GANDIKOTA, 1999-2002 (Box R3894)
    - F 99035 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) MABASA, STANFORD, 1999-2003 (Box R3894)
    - F 99049 - (INDIA) (F-AS) MOHANKUMAR, SUBBARAYALU, 1999-2002 (Box R3894)
    - F 95052 - (KENYA) (F-AS) MURIUKI, ANNE WANJIRU, 1995-2000 (Box R3895)
    - F 96055 - (KENYA) (F-AS) NJUNIE, MICHAEL NGUNJIRI, 1996-2003 (Box R3895)
    - F 97001 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) NGUYEN ANH TUAN, 1997-2002 (Box R3895)
    - F 97025 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) NGUYEN DUY BAY, 1997-2002 (Box R3895)
    - F 97089 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) NGO LUC CUONG, 1997-2002 (Box R3895)
    - F 98015 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) NGUYEN THI THANH THUY, 1998-2000 (Box R3895)
    - F 98051 - (INDIA) (F-AS) MUTHUKRISHNAN, NARAYANAN, 1998-2000 (Box R3895)
    - F 99002 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) NGUYEN THI NGOC HUE, 1999-2004 (Box R3895)
    - F 99032 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) NGUYEN THI NINH THUAN, 1999-2002 (Box R3895)
    - F 99054 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) MVERE, NAOMI NORMA, 1999-2004 (Box R3895)
    - 2000 FS 344 - (THAILAND) (F-AS) PATARAPUWADOL, SUJIN, 2000-2005 (Box R3896)
    - F 95044 - (BANGLADESH) (F-AS) RAHMAN, MUSRUR, 1995-2000 (Box R3896)
    - F 96029 - (IVORY COAST) (F-AS) PITA, JUSTIN-SIMON, 1996-2002 (Box R3896)
    - F 96085 - (MALAWl) (F-AS) PHOMBEYA, HENRY S.K., 1996-1999 (Box R3896)
    - F 97031 - (CHINA) (F-AS) QIAN XIAOYIN, 1997-2000 (Box R3896)
    - F 97044 - (KENYA) (F-AS) NYAMBATI, ELKANA M., 1997-2003 (Box R3896)
    - F 98033 - (INDIA) (F-AS) RAMASAMY, PERUMAL, 1998-2000 (Box R3896)
    - F 98050 - (INDIA) (F-AS) ROHILLA, JAI SINGH, 1998-2001 (Box R3896)
    - F 99003 - (INDONESIA) (F-AS) NUGROHO, SATYA, 1999-2002 (Box R3896)
    - F 99028 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) PHAM THU HANG, 1999-2002 (Box R3896)
    - F 99033 - (CHINA) (F-AS) PENG KAIMAN, 1999-2001 (Box R3896)
    - F 99073 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) PHAM NGOC LUONG, 1999-2002 (Box R3896)
    - F 99090 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) PHAM TRUNG NGHIA, 1999-2005 (Box R3896)
    - F 96015 - (CHINA) (F-AS) YANG WEI, 1996-2001 (Box R3897)
    - F 96074 - (INDONESIA) (F-AS) SEPTININGSIH, ENDANG MULYANI, 1996-2003 (Box R3897)
    - F 96086 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) ZITSANZA, ELLIOT SIMBA, 1996-2001 (Box R3897)
    - F 96095 - (THAILAND) (F-AS) TINJUANGJUN, PORNTIP, 1996-2000 (Box R3897)
    - F 97072 - (INDIA) (F-AS) SHARMA, VIJAY KUMAR, 1997-2001 (Box R3897)
    - F 98003 - (INDIA) (F-AS) SIKKAH, VIRENDRA KUMAR, 1998-2000 (Box R3897)
    - F 98006 - (IVORY COAST) (F-AS) SEMON, MANDE, 1998-2005 (Box R3897)
    - F 99051 - (INDIA) (F-AS) VERMA, DHEERAJ, 1999-2002 (Box R3897)
    - F 99064 - (VIETNAM) (F-AS) TRAN NGOC THACH, 1999-2004 (Box R3897)
    - F 99069 - (INDIA) (F-AS) SANGWAN, VINOD, 1999-2002 (Box R3897)
    - W 88008 - (INDIA)(F-PS) VISHW ANATH, RAMAKRISHNAN (RESCINDED), 1988 (Box R3897)
- AC.2008.066: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2004; AC.2008.066; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3898-R3901.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2008.066.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 99045 - TCE/PACT - COMMUNITY PROBLEM SOLVING, 1991-2004 (Box R3898)
    - RF 99045 - TCE/PACT - COMMUNITY PROBLEM SOLVING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2004 (Box R3898)
    - RF 99045 - TCE/PACT - COMMUNITY PROBLEM SOLVING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2004 (Box R3899)
    - RF 99045 - TCE/PACT - COMMUNITY PROBLEM SOLVING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2004 (Box R3900)
    - RF 99045 - TCE/PACT - COMMUNITY PROBLEM SOLVING - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1991-2004 (Box R3901)